## **Anna Khizhniak**

JUNIOR FRONT-END DEVELOPER
(VUE.JS)

### **Details**

Odessa, Ukraine (I live temporarily in Bucharest, Romania) +380639596624

khizhniak.work@gmail.com

DATE OF BIRTH

33 years

### Links

GitHub

**Portfolio** 

Linkedin

**Telegram** 

#### Skills

Fast Learner

**Communication Skills** 

**Problem Solving** 

Teamwork

Adaptability

### Languages

English

Ukrainian

Russian

Romanian

### **Profile**

I'm junior Front-end developer with experience in HTML, CSS/SASS/SCSS, Javascript/Typescript, React, Vue.js, Node.js. I have been started my education in 2021 and continue practicing through creating my own projects. I have technical degree, so mostly base knowledge I got in the university. My knowledge is nothing without real practice, so I dream to get into a good team, multiply my experience and develop in programming.

I have experience in real project with Vue2.js and finished internship with Javascript/React.

I can say about myself that I like programming because of new challenges all the time. Thats why I've been graduated from the "Node.js" course and also would like to try myself as Full-stack developer.

## **Employment History**

### Front-end developer (Vue.js), remotely

FEBRUARY 2024

- Creating web-pages with custom components
- Work with API, vuex, routing
- Work with mentor
- Communication with command

#### Manager, content manager, copywriter, Online store, Odessa

2017 - 2023

- Add/edit/remove products on web-site
- Add product description
- Communication with suppliers,
- Mailing (with Mailchimp, Sendpulse),
- Work with clients (consulting, selling, orders, delivery control, resolve conflicts).

# Information support center operator, online technical support chat operator, Intertelecom, Odessa

2011 - 2017

- Consulting clients (by phone and online)
- Interacting with other company departments for resolving client issues
- · Selling company services

### Internship, remotely

JULY 2023 - OCTOBER 2023

- PUG
- React
- Javascript
- Adaptive design
- Mentor support

## **Education**

# Bachelor, College of Industrial Automation ONAFT (Technical School of Industrial Automation OSAR), Odessa

2005 - 2009

• Specialty: programmer for automated systems and EOM

### Specialist, Odessa State Environmental University, Odessa

2009 - 2013

Specialty: computer systems engineer

### Hillel "Front-end Pro" course, Odessa

AUGUST 2022 - FEBRUARY 2023

Study: JavaScript, React, Redux, GULP, Webpack, OOP

### Hillel "Front-end Basic" course, Odessa

MAY 2022 - AUGUST 2022

Study: HTML, CSS/SASS/SCSS, GULP

### Hillel "Typescript" course, Odessa

NOVEMBER 2023 - FEBRUARY 2024

Study: Typescript, Jest, design patterns, SOLID, OOP

### Hillel "Node.js" course, Odessa

JANUARY 2024 - APRIL 2024

Study: Node.js, Express, Mongo, Docker, SQLite